[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 17,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_00_B",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 17,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Grace_00",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_01B",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_02_Rumors",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 17,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_01B",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 19,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 20,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Adiana_00",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_03",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 20,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Adiana_00",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 20,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Adiana_00",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_05",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 21,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Adiana_00",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_07",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_06",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "Azoth_Vessel",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 21,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_08",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_07",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 21,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_08",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 23,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 24,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_19",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 24,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Captain",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_19a",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_19",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_20",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_19a",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_21",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_20",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemSolo",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemSolo_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_21_B",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_21_B_Unlock",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemSolo_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemSolo_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemSolo_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "",
        "InProgressResponse": "",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_15_Ritual",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_22",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_21",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_Faction_Vector",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 17,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_Faction_Vector_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99A_Faction_Vector",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_01B",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_Faction_Vector_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@99A_Faction_Vector_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99A_Faction_Vector_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99A_Faction_Vector_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99A_Faction_Vector_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99A_Faction_Vector_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    }
]
